Contact

0633137551 (Mobile) chanchit.ler01@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/chanchitlerdwongsuwan-a9a4511ab (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
.NET Core
Angular
SQL

Chanchit Lerdwongsuwan

Custom Software Engineering Specialist

Bangkok City, Thailand

Summary

Hi, My name is Chanchit Lerdwongsuwan. You can call me Oat. I am 29 years old. I am a Full-Stack developer based in Bangkok, Thailand. I have experience of building Web Applications with Dotnet / Angular and some cool other libraries and frameworks. I am very passionate about improving my coding skills and developing applications and websites. And I hope we can work together on a project. Thank you.

My personal portfolio website: https://frolicking-queijadas-560de5.netlify.app/

Experience

IT One

Custom Software Engineering Specialist October 2021 - Present (3 years 2 months)

Overiew:

As a Custom Software Engineering Specialist, I focus on delivering projects on time by managing the development process, from design to maintenance. I work closely with the team, provide feedback, and ensure smooth communication across all stages of the project. I actively participate in key meetings and help resolve any technical issues to keep projects on track.

Responsibilities:

Project Delivery: Estimate tasks and project timelines to ensure the timely delivery of software solutions, and develop both front-end and back-end tasks according to the project schedule.

Software Development: Design, analyze, develop, and maintain applications in alignment with business needs.

Task Management: Manage task assignments, monitor progress, and provide constructive feedback to team members.

Collaboration & Meetings: Actively participate in requirement gathering, solution design, project kick-offs, and daily stand-ups to ensure smooth project execution.

Issue Resolution: Research and find solutions to help the project and team members resolve issues.

Buzzebees

Back End Developer
July 2021 - September 2021 (3 months)

Overview:

As a Back End Developer, I focus on developing the backend components of projects. I analyze requirements, design databases, and am responsible for developing tasks as assigned. I actively participate in development and attend daily meetings as needed. ensuring the quality and performance of the code.

Responsibilities:

Project Delivery: Estimate and manage tasks as assigned to ensure timely project delivery.

Software Development: Design, analyze, and develop applications in alignment with business needs.

Collaboration & Meetings: Actively participate in development and attend daily meetings as required.

Issue Resolution: Identify solutions to resolve assigned tasks and address technical issues.

Celestica

Full Stack Developer
July 2019 - July 2021 (2 years 1 month)

Overview:

As a Full Stack Developer, I focus on develope, design tasks as assigned Attended meetings or discussion sessions of software team to Performed analysis, design structure project and development of the application according to the user requirements and Attends monthly status meetings with the development, functional and project management teams to discuss status.

Responsibilities:

Project Delivery: Develop assigned tasks for both front-end and back-end according to the project timeline.

Software Development: Design, analyze, and develop applications in alignment with business needs.

Collaboration & Meetings: Actively participate in development and attend daily meetings as required.

Issue Resolution: Identify solutions to resolve issues within assigned tasks.

2fellows

Full Stack Programmer
June 2018 - July 2019 (1 year 2 months)

Thailand

Overview:

As a Full Stack Developer, I focus on developing assigned tasks for both frontend and back-end. I resolve any threats and bugs, communicate with clients to provide knowledge, expertise, and support, and ensure their requirements are met. I also attend client meetings and software team discussions to understand and implement requested new functionalities.

Responsibilities:

Project Delivery: Develop assigned tasks for both front-end and back-end in alignment with the project timeline.

Software Development: Build applications that meet business requirements. Collaboration & Meetings: Actively participate in development and attend daily meetings as needed.

Issue Resolution: Identify and implement solutions to resolve issues within assigned tasks.

Education

Siam University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (August 2014 - June 2018)